(gentle upbeat music)
♪ Here come old flat top,
he come grooving up slowly ♪
♪ He got juju eyeball,
he one holy roller ♪
♪ He got hair down to his knee ♪
♪ Got to be a joker he
just do what he please ♪
(gentle upbeat music continues)
♪ He wear no shoe shine,
he got toe jam football ♪
♪ He got monkey finger,
he shoot Coca-Cola ♪
♪ He say I know you, you know me ♪
♪ One thing I can tell you
is you got to be free ♪
♪ Come together, right now ♪
♪ Over me ♪
♪ He bag production,
he got walrus gumboot ♪
♪ He got Ono sideboard,
he one spinal cracker ♪
♪ He got feet down below his knee ♪
♪ Hold you in his armchair
you can feel his disease ♪
♪ Come together, right now ♪
♪ Over me ♪
♪ Right ♪
(gentle upbeat music continues)
♪ Here comes, uh ♪
♪ Comes, comes ♪
♪ Here comes ♪
♪ He roller coaster,
he got early warning ♪
♪ He got muddy water, he one mojo filter ♪
♪ He say, "One and one and one is three" ♪
♪ Got to be good looking
'cause he's so hard to see ♪
♪ Come together, right now ♪
♪ Over me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
(gentle upbeat music continues)
♪ Come together, yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪